[
  {
    "question": "(x - 5)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 10x + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 5)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 - 10q + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 5)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 10a + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 6)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 - 12n + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 3)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 6x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 6)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 - 12n + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 6)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 - 12z + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 1)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 - 2n + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 4)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 8q + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + 4)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 + 8z + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 5)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 10m + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a - 2)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 4a + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 4)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 8m + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 1)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 2b + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 2)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 4c + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 5)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 + 10y + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 6)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 - 12c + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 2)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 4c + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 5)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 10m + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 1)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 2q + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 6)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 + 12y + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 3)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 - 6z + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 3)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 6p + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 4)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 8x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 6a + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 6)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 12a + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b - 5)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 10b + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 5)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 10p + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 6)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 12m + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 3)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 6c + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b - 3)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 6b + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 6a + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 2)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 + 4y + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 4)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 - 8n + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 5)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 10p + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 4)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 8a + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b - 4)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 8b + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 2)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 - 4c + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 6)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 12q + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 1)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 + 2n + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 2)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 - 4n + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 6)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 - 12n + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 6)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 - 12c + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 4)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 - 8y + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 4)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 8m + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 6)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 - 12z + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 5)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 - 10y + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + 5)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 + 10z + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a - 2)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 4a + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 1)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 - 2y + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 2q)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 4pq + 4q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 3c)^2",
    "answer": "9c^2 + 6cm + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 5x)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 10qx + 25x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - m)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 2my + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 3p)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 - 6cp + 9p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a - y)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 2ay + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 6y)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 + 12xy + 36y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 6z)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 12cz + 36z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + y)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 2ay + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 5y)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 10py + 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + 5y)^2",
    "answer": "25y^2 + 10yz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 5b)^2",
    "answer": "25b^2 + 10bm + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 2z)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 - 4qz + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 3x)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 6cx + 9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 6m)^2",
    "answer": "36m^2 - 12mq + q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 5m)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 - 10cm + 25m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 4c)^2",
    "answer": "16c^2 - 8cz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 6q)^2",
    "answer": "36q^2 - 12qz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 5b)^2",
    "answer": "25b^2 + 10bq + q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b - 5y)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 10by + 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + x)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 2mx + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 4y)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 8py + 16y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - y)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 2py + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 6a)^2",
    "answer": "36a^2 + 12ap + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + 3m)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 + 6mz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 2a)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 - 4am + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 6z)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 12pz + 36z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 6c)^2",
    "answer": "36c^2 - 12cp + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 4b)^2",
    "answer": "16b^2 - 8bp + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 4y)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 8qy + 16y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 3c)^2",
    "answer": "9c^2 - 6cm + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 6m)^2",
    "answer": "36m^2 - 12mx + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - p)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 2pq + q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 5q)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 + 10nq + 25q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 4b)^2",
    "answer": "16b^2 + 8bc + c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 4q)^2",
    "answer": "16q^2 + 8qx + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 5y)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 10py + 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 6b)^2",
    "answer": "36b^2 + 12bq + q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a - 5c)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 10ac + 25c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 5z)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 + 10xz + 25z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 2a)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 - 4ac + c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 3x)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 6cx + 9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 3y)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 6xy + 9y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 5c)^2",
    "answer": "25c^2 + 10cn + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 6q)^2",
    "answer": "36q^2 - 12qx + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - m)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 2mz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 4y)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 - 8cy + 16y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 2m)^2",
    "answer": "4m^2 - 4mq + q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - m)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 2mn + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 4p)^2",
    "answer": "16p^2 - 8pz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3m - 2)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 - 12m + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c + 3)^2",
    "answer": "9c^2 + 18c + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + 5)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 + 10z + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 6)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 12a + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2m - 4)^2",
    "answer": "4m^2 - 16m + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3q - 2)^2",
    "answer": "9q^2 - 12q + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c + 2)^2",
    "answer": "9c^2 + 12c + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p - 5)^2",
    "answer": "4p^2 - 20p + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p - 5)^2",
    "answer": "9p^2 - 30p + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x + 3)^2",
    "answer": "4x^2 + 12x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3z - 3)^2",
    "answer": "9z^2 - 18z + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q - 4)^2",
    "answer": "4q^2 - 16q + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2n - 2)^2",
    "answer": "4n^2 - 8n + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3q - 1)^2",
    "answer": "9q^2 - 6q + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p - 5)^2",
    "answer": "9p^2 - 30p + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3y + 3)^2",
    "answer": "9y^2 + 18y + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3m + 2)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 + 12m + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 5)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 + 10y + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + 4)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 + 8z + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x + 4)^2",
    "answer": "4x^2 + 16x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 1)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 2q + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x + 1)^2",
    "answer": "4x^2 + 4x + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 3)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 6q + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 4)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 8a + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c + 5)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 + 20c + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2n + 2)^2",
    "answer": "4n^2 + 8n + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3z - 6)^2",
    "answer": "9z^2 - 36z + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p - 4)^2",
    "answer": "9p^2 - 24p + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c + 6)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 + 24c + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2y + 3)^2",
    "answer": "4y^2 + 12y + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c - 3)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 - 12c + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3a - 6)^2",
    "answer": "9a^2 - 36a + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2n - 5)^2",
    "answer": "4n^2 - 20n + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 3)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 6p + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 6)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 - 12z + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2y + 4)^2",
    "answer": "4y^2 + 16y + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b + 3)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 + 18b + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3a - 2)^2",
    "answer": "9a^2 - 12a + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 3)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 - 6q + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 1)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 2m + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2n - 4)^2",
    "answer": "4n^2 - 16n + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c - 2)^2",
    "answer": "9c^2 - 12c + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x + 3)^2",
    "answer": "4x^2 + 12x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c + 2)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 + 8c + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 3)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 + 6x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 6a + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3z + 6)^2",
    "answer": "9z^2 + 36z + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2m - 2)^2",
    "answer": "4m^2 - 8m + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3m - 2)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 - 12m + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3m + 6)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 + 36m + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2y + 6m)^2",
    "answer": "36m^2 + 24my + 4y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c - 2b)^2",
    "answer": "4b^2 - 12bc + 9c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a + 5b)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 + 20ab + 25b^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c - 5x)^2",
    "answer": "9c^2 - 30cx + 25x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 2a)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 + 4ap + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2z - 5a)^2",
    "answer": "25a^2 - 20az + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a - 6m)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 - 24am + 36m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3q + 4c)^2",
    "answer": "16c^2 + 24cq + 9q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3n - 6b)^2",
    "answer": "36b^2 - 36bn + 9n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q + 3y)^2",
    "answer": "4q^2 + 12qy + 9y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b - 5p)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 30bp + 25p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3n + 6c)^2",
    "answer": "36c^2 + 36cn + 9n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b - 3c)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 18bc + 9c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p - a)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 4ap + 4p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 2x)^2",
    "answer": "4x^2 + 4xy + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 5m)^2",
    "answer": "25m^2 - 10mz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 5c)^2",
    "answer": "25c^2 - 10cp + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c - 4b)^2",
    "answer": "16b^2 - 24bc + 9c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 2z)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 4qz + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 2q)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 4pq + 4q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a - 4z)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 - 16az + 16z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b + 5a)^2",
    "answer": "25a^2 + 30ab + 9b^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p + 2n)^2",
    "answer": "4n^2 + 8np + 4p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 6p)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 12mp + 36p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2z + 4x)^2",
    "answer": "16x^2 + 16xz + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 4c)^2",
    "answer": "16c^2 - 8cy + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + p)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 2bp + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2m - b)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 4bm + 4m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 4b)^2",
    "answer": "16b^2 - 8bn + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2m + c)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 4cm + 4m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 3z)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 6cz + 9z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2z + 6p)^2",
    "answer": "36p^2 + 24pz + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b - 5m)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 30bm + 25m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c + y)^2",
    "answer": "9c^2 + 6cy + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 3q)^2",
    "answer": "9q^2 - 6qx + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2z - 6x)^2",
    "answer": "36x^2 - 24xz + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 3m)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 + 6mn + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 3m)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 + 6mn + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 4q)^2",
    "answer": "16q^2 - 8qy + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b + 6a)^2",
    "answer": "36a^2 + 36ab + 9b^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3z + 3y)^2",
    "answer": "9y^2 + 18yz + 9z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2z - 5q)^2",
    "answer": "25q^2 - 20qz + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c - m)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 - 4cm + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a - 6y)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 12ay + 36y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x + 2b)^2",
    "answer": "4b^2 + 8bx + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c - 5a)^2",
    "answer": "25a^2 - 30ac + 9c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 2q)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 4mq + 4q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p + 4a)^2",
    "answer": "16a^2 + 24ap + 9p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2y - 4x)^2",
    "answer": "16x^2 - 16xy + 4y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2z - 6p)^2",
    "answer": "36p^2 - 24pz + 4z^2"
  }
]